A Finding Aid to the Lucy R. Lippard Papers, 1930s-2007, bulk 1960s-1990, in the Archives of American Art AAA.lipplucy
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1950s-2006; Series 2; 28.8 Linear feet Boxes 1-28, 51, OVs 54-63
  - Correspondence by Name, 1950s-2006; 2.1
    - Tetamare, Don and Ragna, circa 1970s (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Texas Commission on the Arts and Humanities, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Thea, Carolee, circa 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Tickner, Lisa, 1978-1989 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Timpanelli, Gioia, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Torre, Susana, 1970s-1990s (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Torres, Francesc, circa 1978-1983 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Turyn, Anne, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Twitty, Anne, circa 1970s-circa 1990s (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - T, General: Ta-Te, 1960s-1999 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - T, General: Th-Ti, 1960s-1990s (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - T, General: To, 1960s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - T, General: Tr-Tu, 1960s-1990s (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - T, First Names Only, 1960s-1990s (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Ukeles, Mierle Laderman, 1977-1988 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Ulrichs, Timm, 1960s (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Underhill, Nancy, circa 1980s (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - University of California and University of California Press, 1967-2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - University of Chicago and University of Chicago Press, 1978-1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - University of Colorado, 1970s-1980 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - University of Florida, 1987-2000 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - University of Minnesota, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - University of New Mexico and University of New Mexico Press, 1975-1990 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - University of Oregon, 1987-2004 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - University of Rhode Island, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Urata, Sunao, circa 1965 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Urbach, Marina, circa 1973-circa 1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - U, General, 1960s-2006 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Van Elk, Ger, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Van Raay, Jan, 1974-1985 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Van Saun, John, circa 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Vancouver Art Gallery (Alvin Balkind), 1968-1978 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Varble, Stephen, 1960s-1970s (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Varga, Judy, circa 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Vater, Regina, circa 1970s (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Vazan, Bill, circa 1969-1988 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Vazan, Bill, circa 1973-1981 (Box 19, Folder 27-28)
      Includes photo of Vazan
    - Véhicule Art (Montréal) Inc., 1970s (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Venet, Benar, circa 1966-circa 1972 (Box 19, Folder 30-31)
    - Vergine, Lea, 1971-1980 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Videogalerie Schum, 1960s-1970s (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Viner, Frank Lincoln, 1974-1979 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Viva Latina!, circa 1988-circa 1990; Includes 1 sound cassette of "Woman of Color Meeting Jan 2 90" (Box 19, Folder 35-36)
      Documents relate to an issue of Heresies
    - V, General, Va, 1960s-2005 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - V, General, Ve-Vo, 1960s-1970s (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - V, First Names Only, 1960s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Waisler, Lee, 1980s (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Walker, Kate, circa 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Wall, Jeff, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Wallace, Ian, circa 1970 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Wallace, Michele, 1970s-1990s (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Wapner, Grace, circa 1970-1984 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Weber, John Pitman, 1980s-1990s (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - West East Bag (W.E.B.), 1970s (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Westwater, Angela, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Wexner Center for the Arts, "Ray Johnson: Correspondence" Exhibition Publication, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Wexner Center for the Arts, "Ray Johnson: Correspondence" Exhibition Publication, 1998 (Carton 19, Folder 50-51)
      Contains photocopies of printed material on Ray Johnson used by Lippard while working on her contribution to a publication accompanying the exhibition
    - White, John, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Whitecross, Iain, 1970s-1981 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1960s-1970s (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Wilding, Faith, 1975-1989 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Williams College, 1975-1990 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Wills, Marlene, circa 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Wilson, Ann, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Wilson, Ian, circa 1968-1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Martha, 1974-1979 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Wise, Gillian Ciobotaru, 1977-1988 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Wolin, Ron, circa 1969-circa 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Woman's Building, 1970s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Women's Art Symposium, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Women's Caucus for Art, circa 1972-1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Women's Caucus for Art, 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Women's Caucus for Art, circa 1979 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Women's Caucus for Art, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 10-12)
    - Women's Caucus for Art, circa 1980 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Women's Caucus for Art, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Women's Press Ltd., circa 1978 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Woodward, Tilly, circa 1980s (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - W, General: W.-Wa, 1970s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - W, General: Wea-Wel, 1960s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - W, General: Wer-Wex, 1970s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - W, General: Wh-Wic, 1970s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - W, General: Wie-Williams, 1970s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - W, General: Williamson-Witt, 1970s-1999 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - W, General: Wo, 1970s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - W, General: Wr-Wy, 1970s-1980s (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - W, First Names Only, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - W, Illegible, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - X, General, 1970s-1985 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Yale University, 1969-1992 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Yalter, Nil, 1970s-1980s (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Yang, Gu, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Yates, Marie, 1970s (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - York University, Faculty of Fine Arts, 1973-1980 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Yoshida, Minoru, circa 1968-circa 1975 (Box 20, Folder 33)
      Includes photos of Yoshida; oversized material housed in OV 57
    - Y, General, 1970s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Y, First Names Only, 1970s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Zelasnick, Laura Sue, circa 1980s (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Ziff, Trisha (Santa Monica Museum of Art), 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Zucker, Barbara M., 1970s-1980s (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Zusman, Barbara, 1970s (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Zusman, Barbara, "Putting Mentor Klaw to Bed", 1977 January; 1 Sound cassettes cassette is a copy of an original recording; location of original is unknown. (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Z, General: Za, 1970s-1980s (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Z, General: Ze-Zw, 1960s-1980s (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Z, First Names Only, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Illegible/Unidentified, circa 1960s-circa 1990s (Box 20, Folder 44-45)
    - Illegible/Unidentified, 1960-1978 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Illegible/Unidentified, 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Oversized Alliance for Cultural Democracy housed with Box 1, Folders 26, 34-35 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Arizona State University housed with Box 1, Folder 54 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Art Workers Coalition housed with Box 2, Folder 15 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Baden, Mowry housed with Box 3, Folder 1 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Beuys, Joseph housed with Box 3, Folder 33 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Oversized B, General: Bu housed with Box 4, Folder 27 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Colette housed with Box 5, Folder 19 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Daddaland/Bay Area Daddaists housed with Box 6, Folder 3 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Darboven, Hanne housed with Box 6, Folders 5, 8 and 10 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Graves, Nancy housed with Box 8, Folder 19 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Johnson, Ray, New York Corres- Sponge-Dance School of Vancouver housed with Box 10, Folder 37 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Oversized Kinmont, Bob housed with Box 11, Folder 18 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Oversized Mazzello, Carolyn housed with Box 13, Folder 7 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Oversized N, General: Ni-Ny housed with Box 14, Folder 49 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Oversized Pearson, Henry Hank housed with Box 15, Folder 21 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Oversized Cone, Fred Cornell housed with Box 5, Folder 24 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Oversized Rinke, Klaus housed with Box 16, Folder 25 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Oversized Schapiro, Miriam (Mimi) housed with Box 17, Folder 18 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Oversized Steir, Pat housed with Box 18, Folder 14 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Oversized Tavenner, Pat housed with Box 18, Folder 45 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Oversized T, General: To housed with Box 19, Folder 2 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Oversized Acconci, Vito housed with Box 1, Folders 8 and 10 (Box OV 54)
    - Oversized Alliance for Cultural Democracy housed with Box 1, Folder 38 (Box OV 54)
    - Oversized Art Workers Coalition housed with Box 2, Folders 8-9 (Box OV 54)
    - Oversized Barber, Bruce housed with Box 3, Folder 9 (Box OV 54)
    - Oversized Borofsky, Jonathan housed with Box 3, Folder 49 (Box OV 54)
    - Oversized Burckhardt, Rudolph housed with Box 4, Folder 10 (Box OV 55)
    - Oversized C, General: Cam-Cay housed with Box 5, Folder 42 (Box OV 55)
    - Oversized C, General: Ce housed with Box 5, Folder 43 (Box OV 55)
    - Oversized Glier, Mike housed with Box 8, Folder 9 (Box OV 55)
    - Oversized Gordh, Bill housed with Box 8, Folders 14-15 (Box OV 55)
    - Oversized Graham, Dan housed with Box 8, Folder 18 (Box OV 55)
    - Oversized H, General: Har-Hay housed with Box 9, Folder 55 (Box OV 55)
    - Oversized Kahn, Douglas housed with Box 10, Folder 48 (Box OV 55)
    - Oversized Kaltenbach, Stephen housed with Box 10, Folder 52 (Box OV 55)
    - Oversized Kruger, Barbara housed with Box 11, Folder 32 (Box OV 56)
    - Oversized Kusama,Yayoi housed with Box 11, Folder 38 (Box OV 56)
    - Oversized Les Petites Bon-Bons housed with Box 12, Folder 5 (Box OV 56)
    - Oversized Long, Richard housed with Box 12, Folders 28 and 30 (Box OV 56)
    - Oversized M, General: Mano-Mar housed with Box 13, Folder 49 (Box OV 56)
    - Oversized N. E. Thing Co. (Iain Baxter) housed with Box 14, Folder 17 (Box OV 56)
    - Oversized Nauman, Bruce housed with Box 14, Folder 23 (Box OV 56)
    - Oversized Neuhaus, Max housed with Box 14, Folder 27 (Box OV 56)
    - Oversized Onslow-Ford, Gordon housed with Box 15, Folder 6 (Box OV 56)
    - Oversized Pulsa housed with Box 15, Folder 47 (Box OV 56)
    - Oversized Reid, Terry housed with Box 16, Folder 17 (Box OV 57)
    - Oversized Rupp, Christy housed with Box 16, Folder 48 (Box OV 57)
    - Oversized San Francisco Art Institute housed with Box 17, Folder 10 (Box OV 57)
    - Oversized Shaw, Karen housed with Box 17, Folder 33 (Box OV 57)
    - Oversized Singer, Michael housed with Box 17, Folder 45 (Box OV 57)
    - Oversized Sjoo, Monica housed with Box 17, Folder 46 (Box OV 57)
    - Oversized Walker, Kate housed with Box 19, Folder 31 (Box OV 57)
    - Oversized Yoshida, Minoru housed with Box 20, Folder 33 (Box OV 57)
    - Oversized Arnatt, Keith housed with Box 2, Folder 2 (Box OV 58)
    - Oversized Barry, Robert housed with Box 3, Folders 13-14 (Box OV 58)
    - Oversized Harlam, Meg housed with Box 9, Folder 1 (Box OV 58)
    - Oversized Hompson, Davi Det housed with Box 9, Folder 42 (Box OV 58)
    - Oversized H, General: Hi housed with Box 10, Folder 1 (Box OV 58)
    - Oversized Johnson, Ray housed with Box 10, Folder 33 (Box OV 58)
    - Oversized Judd, Donald housed with Box 10, Folder 39 (Box OV 58)
    - Oversized Kelly, Mary housed with Box 11, Folder 8 (Box OV 58)
    - Oversized Kinmont, Bob housed with Box 11, Folder 18 (Box OV 58)
    - Oversized Louw, Roelof housed with Box 12, Folder 31 (Box OV 58)
    - Oversized Sao Paulo Biennale housed with Box 17, Folder 16 (Box OV 59)
    - Oversized Sharon, Miriam housed with Box 17 Folders 27 and 30 (Box OV 59)
    - Oversized Streeter, Tal housed with Box 18, Folder 18 (Box OV 59)
    - Oversized W, General: Wie-Williams housed with Box 20, Folder 21 (Box OV 59)
    - Oversized Z, General: Za housed with Box 20, Folder 41 (Box OV 59)
    - Oversized Beuys, Joseph housed with Box 3, Folder 33 (Box OV 60)
    - Oversized Byars, James Lee housed with Box 4 Folder 16 (Box OV 60)
    - Oversized Kawara, On housed with Box 11, Folder 6 (Box OV 60)
    - Oversized Kossuth, Joseph housed with Box 11 Folder 25 (Box OV 60)
    - Oversized LeWitt, Sol housed with Box 12, Folders 12, 14 and 16 (Box OV 61)
    - Oversized L, General: Lu-Ly housed with Box 12, Folder 42 (Box OV 61)
    - Overszied Pezole, Frederike housed with Box 15, Folder 26 (Box OV 61)
    - Overszied Rosenquist, James housed with Box 16, Folders 37-38 (Box OV 61)
  - Correspondence by Subject, 1950s-1990s; 2.2
    This series primarily documents Lipppard's engagement with social and political issues and groups working for change through activism and art. While much of the content comprises printed material on issues such as artists rights, censorship, U. S. policy in Central Americal, conceptual art, public art, and reproductive rights, these files are interespersed with correspondence with related individuals including artists, photographic material, and some of Lippard's related notes and writings. For example, folders on conceptual art include a draft manuscript for Lippard's essay Escape Attempts. Folder headings are generally derived from those used by Lippard.
    Records on Central America include material relating to the Nicaraguan Cultural Alliance. A group of folders concerning non-U.S. galleries document Lippard's interaction with artists and galleries overseas, including European and Austrialian galleries and the Centro de Arte y Comunicacíon in Buenos Aires where Lippard's third "numbers show" "2,972,453," was held in 1971.
    Note that the 5 folders on "Jobs" relate specifically to work opportunities offered to Lippard such as speaking engagements and participation on committees, juries and panels.
    Mail art folders comprise a mixture of printed material including copies of the Balloon Newspaper, and correspondence from mail art and fluxus artists such as Fletcher Copp and Ken Friedman.
    Mail art records also include the results of Ray Johnson's mailing, "Send Slips to Lucy Lippard," which Johnson apparently undertook after Lippard omitted him from her book Pop Art (1966). Following this "slip" she was the recipient of various interpretations of the word including an actual slip to wear.
    Series includes 1 recording on 1 sound cassette.
    - Abstract Expressionism, 1950s-1960s (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - AIDS, Censorship and Exhibitions, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 49-50)
    - All America's Dialogue, 1980s (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
    - All America's Dialogue, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - All America's Dialogue, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
    - Alternative Movements/Spaces, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Oversized material housed in OV 62
    - Alternative Movements/Spaces, 1959; 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Alternative Movements/Spaces, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Alternative Movements/Spaces, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Alternative Movements/Spaces, 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Architectural and Environmental Art, circa 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      Oversized material housed in OV 63
    - Art and Language, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Art and Language, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Art and Language, 1968-1971 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Art and Language, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Art and Politics, circa 1972 (Box 21, Folder 17-18)
    - Art by Working Class, circa 1982-1985 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Art Strike, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Artists Rights/Artists Contracts, 1970s (Box 21, Folder 21)
      Oversized material housed in Box 51 Folder 6
    - Australia, circa 1974-1983 (Box 21, Folder 22-23)
    - Black Liberation Movement, circa 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 24-25)
    - Carnegie Mellon University, MFA Program, circa 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Cartoons, circa 1976-1987 (Box 21, Folder 27-28)
    - Cartoons, 1976-1981 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Cartoons, 1982-1987 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Censorship, 1979-1988; 1966 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Censorship, circa 1989 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Censorship, 1989 April-June (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Censorship, 1989 July-August (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Censorship, 1989 September (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Censorship, 1989 October-December (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Censorship, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Censorship, 1990 January-February (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Censorship, 1990 March-May (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Censorship, 1990 June (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Censorship, 1990 July (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Censorship, 1990 August-September (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Censorship, 1990 October-December (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Censorship Emergency, circa 1987-1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Center for Constitutional Rights, circa 1987-1992 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Central America, circa 1984-1988 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Central America, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Central America, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Central America, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Central America, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Central America, Printed Material, circa 1970-1989 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Central America, Printed Material, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Central America, Printed Material, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Central America, Printed Material, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Central America, Printed Material, 1974-1979 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Central America, Printed Material, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Central America, Printed Material, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Central America, Printed Material, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Central America, Printed Material, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 24-26)
    - Central America, Printed Material, 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Central Europe, circa 1969-1970s (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Central Europe, circa 1970 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      Includes photos of artwork by artists Peter Stembera and Karel Miler; oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 6
    - Central Europe, circa 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Central Europe, circa 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Central Europe, circa 1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Central Europe, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 4-5)
    - Central Europe, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Chile, circa 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
    - China, circa 1980 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Color Cartoons (Jerry Kearns), 1982-circa 1987 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Color Cartoons (Jerry Kearns), circa 1987-1989 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Columbia, circa 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Columbus and Art Quincentennial, circa 1980s-circa 1990s (Box 23, Folder 13-15)
    - Columbus and Art Quincentennial, circa 1989-1993 (Box 23, Folder 16-17)
    - Columbus and Art Quincentennial, 1985-1988; 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Columbus and Art Quincentennial, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Columbus and Art Quincentennial, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Columbus and Art, Quincentennial, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 21-24)
    - Columbus and Art, Quincentennial, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 25-28)
    - Columbus and Art, Quincentennial, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 29-30)
    - Columbus and Art, Quincentennial, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
    - Conceptual Art, circa 1969-1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Conceptual Art, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Conceptual Art, 1984-1990 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Conceptual Art, 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Corporations and Culture (Business and Art), circa 1979-1986 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Criticism, circa 1980-1990 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Cuban Paintings Lawsuit, Ashton vs. Newcomb, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Culture and Politics, General, circa 1976-1982 (Box 24, Folder 11-12)
    - Culture, Costa Rica and Honduras, circa 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Culture, El Salvador, circa 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Culture, Nicaragua, circa 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Cutlture, Nicaragua, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Culture, Nicaragua, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - "Death Show," New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Disabled Artists, circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Disabled Artists, 1981-1988 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Ecology, circa 1970 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - El Salvador, circa 1984 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - El Salvador, Benefit Exhibitions and Sales, 1990s (Box 24, Folder 23-24)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 25-26)
    - Erotic Art, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 27-28)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, FOIA, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Feminism, circa 1974 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Films, circa 1985 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Films, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Fluxus, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Folk Art, circa 1982-1992 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Ford Foundation Grant Applications, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Galleries, Argentina, 1960s-1970s (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Galleries, Australia, circa 1970-1974 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Galleries, Belgium, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Galleries, Canada, 1970s-1980s (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Galleries, Denmark, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Galleries, England, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Galleries, Finland, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Galleries, France, 1960s-1970s (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Galleries, Germany, 1960s-1970s (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Galleries, Holland, 1960s-1970s (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Galleries, Italy, 1960s-1970s (Box 25, Folder 4-6)
    - Galleries, Japan, 1960s-1970s (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Galleries, Switzerland, 1970s (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Global Forum at Sundance, "Crossing Borders", 1991 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Guggenheim Fellowships, circa 1980s; circa 1968 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Housing, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Humor, circa 1980-1988 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Jobs, circa 1986-1990 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Jobs, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Jobs, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 15-16)
    - Jobs, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Labor and Art, circa 1979-1987 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Labor and Art, 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Labor and Art, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Labor and Art, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Labor and Art, 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Mail Art, circa 1960-1980 (Box 25, Folder 23-24)
    - Mail Art, 1960-1970 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Mail Art, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Mail Art, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Mail Art, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Mail Art, 1975-1980 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Mail Art, Northwest Mounted Valise, circa 1970s (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Mail Art, Northwest Mounted Valise, circa 1971-circa 1972 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Mail Art, Send Slips to Lucy Lippard, circa 1967-circa 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Mail Art, Send Slips to Lucy Lippard, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Mail Art, Send Slips to Lucy Lippard, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Mail Art, Send Slips to Lucy Lippard, 1970-1974; 1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Media Analysis/Imagery, circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 6
    - Media Analysis/Imagery, 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Media Analysis/Imagery, 1984-1987 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Murals and Paintings on Doors, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Murals and Paintings on Doors, 1975-1979 (Box 26, Folder 9)